Total Experience: 6 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]



Software developer seeking Roles in Software Development ,Application Programming and Web Development using Microsoft Technologies.



Current Designation: Techology Lead

Current Company: Infosys

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad

Pref. Location: Vijayawada, Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: asp.net web api,asp.net mvc,sql server,c#

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 11-Apr-20 Last Modified: 16-Mar-20

### Summary

6 years experience on Microsoft Technologies.

Good in developing web applications / web services in Microsoft Visual Studio .Net IDE using ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET WFB API.

Good working knowledge on SQL Server.

Good knowledge of OOP concepts.

### Work Experience

Infosys as Techology Lead Feb 2019 to Till Date

ADP India Pvt Ltd as Member Technical

Jun 2017 to Feb 2019

Working a software engineer and my responsibility is to develop applications using ASP.NET WEB API, MVC

Lexicon Infotech Ltd as Senior Software Engineer

Feb 2014 to Jun 2017

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from eswar college of engineering in 2013

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
C# .NET,HTML	
ASP.NET MVC 5, ASP.NET Web API 2	
JavaScript, JQuery	
Visual Studio 2013, VS2015	
VS 2013, VS 2017	

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Telugu				

# **Affirmative Action**

Physically Challenged: No Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time

**Work Authorization**